Minh Nguyen

Marketing Coordinator / Graphic+Web Designer

Phone: (512) 825 9661

Email: MinhStudios@gmail.com
Portfolio: www.Minhstudios.com
Linkedin.com/in/minhstudios

Summary

Minh Nguyen is a graphic designer with 6 years professional experience with a focus in print, illustration, logo and web design. He also has experience with Wordpress, Bootstrap, real estate photography, and drawing. Minh aims to have a continued advancement in web development as part of his goal set. Originally from Austin-Texas, he attended Texas State University, gaining his Bachelors of Fine Arts. After completing an internship in San Antonio (Clockwork Studios), Minh began working in-house for a Real Estate firm where he was immersed in website design, real estate photography, print, and direct campaign. Currently he works with Newmark Knight Frank in high asset multifamily sales as a marketing coordinator. With a passion to always grow and become a better designer, he is open and available for any multi-faceted project needs.

Experience

MARKETING COORDINATOR | DEC 2017 - SEPT 2020 Newmark Knight Frank, Austin, TX

- » Marketed over +\$1 billion in multifamily in real estate transactions
- » Create proposals & offer memorandums for multi-million dollar properties
- » Market overview research and coordination of team to client projects

GRAPHIC DESIGNER (CONTRACTOR) | NOV 2017 - May 2018 Texas Hospital Association, Austin, TX

» Producing White Pages, layouts, editing, logos, and other print materials

GRAPHIC+WEB DESIGNER / PHOTOGRAPHER | NOV 2014 - NOV 2017 The Carvajal Group, Austin, TX

- » Design fliers, brochures, banners, direct mail, logos and print materials
- » Creating and maintain Wordpress website periodically for listings
- » Real estate photography and post-editing for listings
- » Create MLS signs, billboard graphics, and magazine ads

INTERN GRAPHIC DESIGNER | JAN 2012 - MAY 2012 Clockwork Studios, San Antonio, TX

- » Edits to client projects and finalization
- » Creating solution to client projects with brainstorming
- » Logo and campaign branding creation

Education

WEB DESIGN | 2016 - 2017

Austin Community College & Udemy.com | Austin, TX (Post bachelors education)

COMMUNICATION DESIGN | 2006 - 2010

Bachelors of Fine Arts | Texas State University | San Marcos, TX Cum Laude Achievement | GPA: 3.7/4.0

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- » Dean's List 2010
- » Dean's List 2009
- » High achievements in Printmaking
- » High achievements in Sculpture & Drawing

Skillset / Abilities

Design Softwares: Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Dreamweaver, Flash, and Premiere

Web-based Application: HTML/CSS, FTP Client and Wordpress

Hand skills: Drawing, Painting, and Printmaking

Office Application: Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Office 365, Mac, Windows, and Excel

Photography: Real Estate Photography and Lightroom CC post editing

Campaign E-blast Interface: Listing Lab

References

Shawn Meeks

Design Professor at Fort Lewis College (Durango, Co) 210.382.9091 | scmeek@fortlewis.edu

Erik Le

Operational Manager at Leadspace (Austin, Tx) 512.998.3944 | erik.le1082@gmail.com

Angela Clapper

Facilities Coordinator II at HID Global (Austin, Tx) 512.627.1000 | angela.clapper@hidglobal.com

Jose Luis Salazar

UX Developer at Community Impact Newspaper (Austin, Tx) 512.940.8604 | choche_@hotmail.com